import React from 'react'

let horrorQuotes = {
    title: "Horror Quotes",
    questions: [
        {
            question: "Have to Checked the Children is a quote from this movie",
            answers: ["Scream", "The Shining", "When a Stranger Calls", "The Mist"],
            correct: "When a Stranger Calls"
        },
        {
            question: "It will tear your soul apart is a quote from this movie",
            answers: ["Hellraiser", "Psycho", "Alien", "Saw"],
            correct: "Hellraiser"
        },
        {
            question: "I could help you, but I'd rather stand here and record is a quote from this movie",
            answers: ["The Blair Witch story", "Invasion of the Body Snatchers", "The Texas Chainsaw Massacres", "The Fog"],
            correct: "The Blair Witch story"
        },
        {
            question: "This tagline is from the movie Poltergeist",
            answers: ["Their past has come back to haunt them", "Fear Changes Everything", "They're here", "Live or Die. Make your choice"],
            correct: "They're here"
        },
        {
            question: "Come on into the water is a quote from this film",
            answers: ["Saw", "Jaws", "The Fog", "The Haunting"],
            correct: "Jaws"
        },
        {
            question: "Let the games begin is a tagline from this movie",
            answers: ["Saw", "The Exorcist", "The Omen", "Friday the 13th"],
            correct: "Saw"
        },
        {
            question: "Look, he's a twitcher is a line from this scary movie",
            answers: ["Dawn of the Dead", "The Silence of the Lambs", "The Fog", "Invasion of the Body Snatchers"],
            correct: "Dawn of the Dead"
        },
        {
            question: "The Devil Inside was the tagline for this movie",
            answers: ["The Omen", "Rosemary's baby", "The Exorcist", "The Hills have Eyes"],
            correct: "The Exorcist"
        },
        {
            question: "This film claimed You don't have to believe....just beware",
            answers: ["Poltergeist", "Candyman", "Pet Sematary", "The Thing"],
            correct: "Candyman"
        },
        {
            question: "This movie tells you that now there is name for terror",
            answers: ["Cujo", "Carrie", "Christine", "Rosemary's baby"],
            correct: "Cujo"
        },
        {
            question: "It's a full moon..... is a line from this movie",
            answers: ["Videodrome", "American Werewolf in London", "The Haunting", "The Beyond"],
            correct: "American Werewolf in London"
        },
        {
            question: "Sleep kills according to the quote from this movie",
            answers: ["Nightmare on Elm Street", "Silence of the Lambs", "Tooth Fairy", "The Amityville Horror"],
            correct: "Nightmare on Elm Street"
        },
        {
            question: "For God's sake, get out is a qote from this movie",
            answers: ["The Omen", "The Exorcist", "The Amityville Horror", "Psycho"],
            correct: "The Amityville Horror"
        },
        {
            question: "Do you have any vacancies is a quote from this movie",
            answers: ["Jaws", "The Shining", "Psycho", "1408"],
            correct: "Psycho"
        },
        {
            question: "Swing away Merrill is a quote from this movie",
            answers: ["Ghost Story", "Signs", "Sixth Sense", "Cujo"],
            correct: "Signs"
        },
    ]
}

export default horrorQuotes